饑餓
的青春
第二季  第十六集
0,0,0,fx,學習
0,0,0,fx,分享
0,0,0,fx,進步
本字幕由ZiMuZu原創翻譯
最新下載請登錄www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻譯   冰藍     aaaBao
翻譯  roaddog    妖精希亞
校對  roaddog
時間軸 aaaBao
后期 斯人       總監 roaddog
打開微信   掃描左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    ustvboom
了解最新影視字幕發布信息
謝謝你載我過來  尤蘭達
Thanks for giving me a ride, Yolanda.
我保證  等索菲亞找到工作
I promise, as soon as Sofia gets a job,
我的車就回來了
I will have my car back.
沒事啦
Oh, that's okay.
這樣我不用伯特·雷諾茲的
It lets me drive in the carpool lane
充氣娃娃  也能在拼車車道行駛了
without having to use my Burt Reynolds blowup doll.
各位
Well...
這是你們都在期待的時刻
It's the moment you've all been waiting for.
等等
Wait a minute.
你昨晚去了高大上的慈善晚會
You went to a fancy charity function last night.
我聞到了富人的東西
I smell rich people things.
是禮包嗎
Ooh, is it a swag bag?
拜托告訴我是禮包
Please tell me it's a swag bag.
也許吧
Maybe.
等等  我不明白  怎么回事
Wait, I don't get it. What's going on?
每次我去參加大型宴會
Every time I go to a big event
他們都會送我一禮品袋的好東西
I get this gift bag full of really cool stuff
我會分給艾略特和尤蘭達
and I let Elliot and Yolanda divvy it up.
但現在加比來了  所以得你們三個分
But now Gabi's here, so you gotta split it three ways.
-討厭  -該死
- Oh, man. - Son of a bitch.
好了  我們保持文明
All right, let's keep it civilized.
記住  我走后才能開始分
And remember, it doesn't start until I leave the room.
天啊
Oh, my goodness!
這是什么  這是什么
What is it? What is it?
杜嘉班納墨鏡
Ooh, Dolce & Gabbana sunglasses.
智能手表
A smartwatch!
攝像機
A video camera?
十節動感單車課
A 10-pack for soul spin classes!
你為什么要去上動感單車課
Why would you go to a spin class?
你去吃自助餐都上氣不接下氣
You get winded walking down the buffet line.
杰克·吉倫哈爾先生在舊金山拍電影
Mr. Jake Gyllenhaal is in San Francisco filming a movie.
他來城里時就去這家健身房
This is the place he goes to spin when he's in town.
謝天謝地  我們有攝像機
Thank goodness we got a video camera!
瞧  皇家酒店和水療中心的一百美金禮券
Look, a $100 gift certificate to the Royal Hotel and Spa.
-你賺了  -那是最好的
- Oh no, you score. - That is the best.
有十張呢
Whoa, 10 of them.
-我的  -我的  我的
- Mine. - Mine. Mine.
-我的  我的  -我的  我的
- Mine. Mine. Mine. - Mine. Mine.
我的  我的
Mine. Mine.
-我的  我的  -我的  我的
- Mine. Mine. Mine... - Mine. Mine. Mine...
今天工作找得怎么樣了
Hey, so how'd this job search go today?
挺好的
Oh, great.
所以我在用一大袋
You know, that's why I'm celebrating
棉花糖來慶祝
with a big bag of marshmallows.
你做的這張漂亮地圖上
Hey, what's with all the little pins
為什么按了這么多大頭針啊
on this pretty map you made?
那是為了記錄
Oh, that's just to keep track
我申請的所有地方
of all the places I've applied...
真棒
That's fantastic.
然后被拒絕了
...and got rejections from.
記住  索菲亞  只要一個雇主同意就行了
Remember, Sofia, it only takes one employer to say yes.
的確有雇主同意了
Well, one employer did say yes.
-真棒  -就是我爸
- Yay! - It was my dad.
他覺得我應該回到佛羅里達州
Yeah, he thinks I should move back home to Florida,
為他工作
and work for him.
索菲亞  你不能回家
Aww, Sofia, you can't go home.
加比  我都失業三個月了
Gabi, I've been unemployed for three months.
已經窮途末路了
I'm at the end of my rope.
我都買不起更多的大頭針了
I can't even afford any more rejection pins.
好  夠了
Okay, okay, enough, all right?
把這張悲慘的地圖拿到一邊
Let's put the sad map away.
你得離開這間公寓  找點樂子
You need to get out of this apartment and have some fun.
我沒心情找樂子
I'm not in the mood for fun.
如果我告訴你
Well, what if I told you
我有皇家酒店和水療中心的
that I have $1,000 worth of gift certificates
一千美金禮券呢
to the Royal Hotel and Spa.
-可以美甲  -美甲
- Thinking mani-pedis. - Mani-pedis?
-美發  -美發
- Blow outs. - Blow outs?
也許來個按摩
Maybe a massage.
-按摩  -是啊
- A massage? - Yeah.
化妝打扮一番  最后在酒吧喝杯好酒
A total makeover ending with fancy drinks at the bar.
好酒  好棒
Fancy drinks? Yay!
那肯定是我今天第一杯酒
That'll totally be my first drink of the day.
走吧
Let's go!
瞧  我說這會讓你高興的
See. I told you this would cheer you up.
加比  你說得對
Gabi, you were so right.
我沒錢  沒工作
I mean, I have no money, no job,
可能得回到佛羅里達州
and I'll probably still have to move home to Florida,
但我喜歡我的新煙熏妝
But I love my new smoky eyes.
我喜歡你的新態度
And I love your new attitude.
你說些什么呢
What are you talking about?
我只是在說
I'm just saying, you know,
過去的幾個月里  你努力找工作
these past few months of you trying to get a job
讓你變得有些...消極
has made you kinda negative.
我能說什么啊  我生命中的一切都好糟糕
Well, what can I tell you? Everything in my life sucks.
我只是說我覺得你該改變現狀
I'm just saying I think you need to start shaking things up.
解放思想  敞開懷抱接受生活
Think outside the box. Start saying yes to life
和新事物
and new things...
比如那邊的小哥
Like that guy over there.
他從你坐下來開始就一直盯著你了
You know he's been staring at you since you sat down.
天啊
Oh, my god.
現在你的機會來了
Okay. Now's your chance.
去做索菲亞絕不會做的事
Do something Sofia would never do.
大膽點  瘋狂點  去跟他說話
Be bold. Be crazy. Go talk to him.
我還是等他來找我好了
You know what? I'm just gonna wait for him to come to me.
像是等待那些雇主
Oh, like you're waiting for all those employers
來找你  跟你說話嗎
to come and talk to you?
這就是我的意思
See, this is what I mean.
你得采取行動  搞到艷遇
You need to take action and get some action.
知道嗎  你說得對
You know what? You're right.
我還有什么可失去的呢
Like, what do I have to lose?
-沒有  因為你一無所有  -對
- Nothing. 'Cause you got nothing. - Yeah.
你還要酒嗎
Can I get you another round?
好  再來一杯伏特加蔓越莓加冰
Uh, yeah, I'll have another vodka cran on ice.
這張優惠券僅限于食物
This coupon is only good for food.
好吧  來點冰就行
Okay, just the ice then.
天啊  加比  管用了
My god, Gabi, it worked!
他邀請我去吃晚餐  我同意了
He asked me to dinner, and I said... yes.
真棒  這應該慶祝一下
That's great! This calls for a celebration.
我請大家喝冰
Ice for everyone!
根據杰克·吉倫哈爾公關所說
Okay, according to Jake Gyllenhaal's publicist,
他上的就是這里的動感單車課
this is the spin class he goes to.
你看到他時冷靜一點
When you see him, be cool.
別做讓我丟臉的事
Don't do anything to embarrass me.
是他  天啊  天啊
It's him! Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god!
你怎么知道  這里好黑
How can you tell? It's so damn dark in here.
等等
Oh, wait.
是我戴了我的杜嘉班納墨鏡
I had on my new Dolce & Gabbana sunglasses.
我要拍張跟他一起健身的照片
I need my picture taken working out with him
這樣就能跟朋友們吹噓  從而提高地位了
so I can brag to my friends and elevate my status.
這就是大家都在說的嗎
This is what everybody's talking about?
一些健身腳踏車
A bunch of stationary bikes?
各位  我是騎自行車過來的
Guys, I rode a bike to get here.
這太差勁了  我走了
This is lame. I'm out.
-誰想來騎車啊  -我
- Who's ready for a spin? - Me.
我準備好騎車了  我是喬什
I am ready for a spin. I'm Josh.
你經常在這里嗎
Do you spin here often?
每天都來  這是我的工作
Every day. It's my job.
好吧
All right.
等等  你倆
Wait. You two.
你們從來沒上過動感單車課  對吧
You've never been to a spin class, have you?
你怎么知道的
How can you tell?
因為我有眼睛
Because I have eyes.
初學者[處女]去后排
Spin virgins go to the back row.
有人嘲笑我是處女
I'm being made fun of for being a virgin?
高中的情景又重演了
It's like high school all over again.
真棒
Hey, great.
現在我們怎么和杰克拍照啊
Now how are we gonna get our photo taken with Jake?
聽過自拍桿嗎  小婊砸
You ever heard of a selfie stick, bitch?
瞧瞧誰終于回家了
Look who's finally home.
我接受了你的建議
I took your advice,
擁抱了生活  晚餐和甜點
and I said yes to life, to dinner, and to, um... dessert.
是焦糖甜點還是"叫床"甜點
Was it like ice cream dessert, or you scream dessert?
天啊  我之前從沒做過這種事
Oh my god, you know, I've never done that before.
我是說  我做過啦
I mean, I've done that before,
但沒有這樣過
but never like that, you know?
我是個好女孩
I'm a nice girl
但做了壞女孩的事
who did a bad girl thing.
我真為你驕傲
I'm so proud of you.
你太對了
You were so right!
放手太好玩了
Letting go is fun.
我對生活說了"好"
I said yes to life,
結果找到了一個有趣迷人
and found a funny, charming, and uh,
非常浪漫的男人
very romantic guy.
他給我留了一張便條
Aww, he left me a note.
我跟你說了他很浪漫嗎
Did I tell you he was romantic?
快打開  上面寫的什么
Open it, open it! What's it say?
是五百塊
It's $500.
他為什么給你五百...
Well, why would he give you 500--
天啊  他不會覺得我是...
Oh my god, you don't think he thinks I'm--
不  他沒覺得你是...
No, I don't think he thinks you're--
你覺得他是怎么想的
What did you think that he thought?
-我是個妓女  -我也是這么想的
- That I'm a hooker? - Yeah, that's what I thought.
天啊
Oh, my god!
不  沒事的  沒事的
No, it's okay, it's okay! It's all right, hey.
往好的方面看
Look on the bright side...
至少你終于找到工作了
At least you finally got a job.
天啊  我成妓女了
Oh my god, I'm a hooker.
不
No!
你才不是妓女  他以為你是而已
You're not a hooker, he just thought you were.
-這都怪你  加比  -怪我嗎
- This is your fault, Gabi. - My fault?
沒錯  "擁抱生活  索菲亞"
Yes! "Say yes to life, Sofia."
我擁抱了生活
Well, I said yes to life,
現在成了只有七十八塊存款的妓女
and now I'm just a ho with $78 in her bank account.
實際上是五百七十八塊
Technically, $578.
閉嘴  我不會要那錢的
Shut up, shut up! I'm not gonna keep that money.
那是臟錢  骯臟的錢
That's dirty! That's dirty, dirty money.
我覺得這是個很搞笑的故事
Come on, I think this is gonna be a really funny story
-可以說給孩子...  -就是這個  加比
to tell your kids one day. No, this is it. This is it, Gabi!
這是老天告訴我要回到佛羅里達州
This is the universe telling me to move back home to Florida.
我破產了  而且崩潰了
I'm just-- I'm totally broke, and totally broken.
你會沒事的  我們會想辦法的
Aww, you're gonna be fine, we'll figure something out.
當遇到難關時  我以前總是告訴自己
You know, when things were tough, I used to tell myself,
"至少你不是個妓女"
"Well, at least you're not a hooker."
現在都沒法這樣說了
Now I can't even say that.
可以說啊  只是那不是真的了
Well, you can, it just won't be true.
讓我搞明白
Let me get this straight,
你站在索菲亞旁邊
you were standing right next to Sofia,
結果別人覺得她才是妓女嗎
and someone thought she was the prostitute?
艾略特  這事很嚴肅好嗎  索菲亞真的很難過
Elliot, this is serious, okay? Sofia's really devastated.
至少她能舉起她的腿
Well, at least she can lift her legs.
還能為此收錢
And get paid for it.
你倆怎么覺得
What possessed you two to think
你們能挺過一整節動感單車課啊
you could get through an entire class of soul spin?
你們拍到杰克·吉倫哈爾的照片了嗎
Did you at least get a picture of Jake Gyllenhaal?
差不多吧  我只拍到了他的一只腳
Sort of. All I got was one of his foot.
他的腳好大啊
He's got some big feet.
那是我的腳  蠢貨
That's my foot, fool!
猜猜誰跟那個美女單車教練約會了
Guess who's got a date with that hot spin instructor?
我啊
This guy!
等等  你跟我們上了一樣的課
Wait, how did you take the same class we did
你怎么還能走啊
and you're still walking?
我每天都鍛煉  而且吃得很健康
Well, I exercise every day and I eat right.
那就是我們不同的地方
Well, that's where we differ.
喬什  我能跟你談談嘛
Um, Josh, can I talk to you about something?
今天大家都想找我啊
Everybody wants a piece of me today, huh?
我真受歡迎
Popular guy.
說吧
Talk to me.
這事很嚴肅
Okay, this is kind of serious.
我能跟貼心不自大的喬什談談嗎
Can I get sweet Josh or not-cocky Josh?
沒問題  怎么了  親愛的
You got it. What's wrong, babe?
那有點太娘了
That was kind of a halfsie.
怎么了
What's going on?
索菲亞想著要回佛羅里達州了
Sofia's thinking of moving home to Florida
因為她昨晚跟一個男人睡了
because she slept with a guy last night
他把她當成妓女了
who thought she was a hooker.
真是沒料到
Did not see that one coming.
我得做些什么來改變這一切
I have to do something, something that's gonna turn this around.
我不知道該做什么  你知道嗎
And I don't know what that something is. Do you?
好吧  那可是索菲亞
Okay, look, it's Sofia we're talking about here.
肯定出了什么差錯
There's obviously some kind of mistake.
他們做完愛后  他往她的包包里塞進個
Well, he slipped an envelope with $500 in her purse
裝了五百塊的信封
after they had sex.
也許那是給別人的呢
Maybe it was meant for someone else?
信封上有她的名字嗎
Was her name on the envelope?
沒有
No.
有便條嗎
Was there a note?
沒有
No.
那錢可能是給別人的啊
So, the money could have been for anybody.
他也許是留給管家的
He could have left it for housekeeping.
或是助理  博彩經紀人的啊
Or maybe his assistant, or his bookie.
天吶  你說的沒錯
My God, you're right!
索菲亞不是妓女  只是小偷而已
Sofia's not a hooker, she's just a thief.
你好  你還記得昨晚我們見過嗎
Hi. Do you remember me from last night?
當時我和朋友在一起  她穿短裙
I was with my friend-- short dress,
細高跟  化煙熏妝
stilettos, smoky eyes?
那個妓女啊
Oh, the hooker.
她不是妓女  你怎么會這么想呢
She's not! Why would you think that?
因為她穿短裙  細高跟  化煙熏妝
Short dress, stilettos, smoky eyes.
好吧  她不是妓女  她很可愛
Okay, she's not a hooker. She's lovely.
-人很好  -讓我猜猜
- She's super sweet-- - Let me guess.
-心地善良  -不對
- Heart of gold? - No!
心地的確善良
I mean, yes.
但重點是
But, the point is
經歷了昨晚的誤會之后
that after last night's misunderstanding
她很傷心  在考慮搬回佛州老家
she's so upset that she's considering moving home to Florida
去她爸爸的雜貨店上班
to work at her father's grocery store.
收銀妹子
Ooh, checkout girl.
那是我的性幻想之一
That's one of my fantasies.
別鬧了
Stop it.
她是我最好的朋友  我不能讓她搬回家
She's my best friend, and I'm not letting her move home.
所以照我說的做  好嗎
So, here's what we're gonna do, okay?
你錄段話給她
You're gonna record a message to her,
說她在包里找到的信封
saying that the envelope that she found in her purse
是從床頭柜上掉進她包里的
must have fallen off the night stand
因為那本來是要給管家的
because it was meant for housekeeping.
準備  說吧
Okay, ready, go!
很抱歉你的朋友不開心
I'm sorry your friend's upset,
但我不會錄的
but I'm not recording anything.
我怎么知道你不是警察
How do I know you're not a cop?
什么意思  你的另一個變態性幻想嗎
What is that? Like another one of your sick fantasies?
我是名廚師
I'm a chef.
雖然這性幻想也不錯
Even though that's kind of hot, too.
我是喬什·卡明斯基先生的私人廚師
I am the personal chef to Mr. Josh Kaminski.
喬什·卡明斯基  那位軟件開發嗎
Josh Kaminski? The software developer?
對  他好像是做這個的
Yeah, I think that's what he does.
我是星光郵輪公司的區域主管
I am the regional director for Star Bright Cruises.
周四晚上我要舉辦船長晚宴
I'm hosting the captain's dinner Thursday night,
而我的宴會承辦剛剛不干了
and my caterer just dropped out.
你有空來嗎
You by any chance available?
真的嗎  不  我絕不會為你工作的
Seriously? No, I would never work for you.
絕不
Never ever.
酬勞是五千塊
The gig pays five grand.
做新派亞洲菜怎么樣
How does Asian fusion sound?
真不敢相信
I still can't believe
那是你第一次上動感單車課
that that was your first time in spin class.
你真是個運動健將
You're quite an athlete.
我從沒有把自己當作一個運動員
Well, you know, I've never referred to myself as an athlete,
但既然你這么說了  這個描述非常準確
but, now that you mention it, it's pretty accurate.
我想我喜歡的都是同一類人
I guess I have a type.
我之前的四個男友都是打籃球的
The last four guys I dated were all basketball players.
籃球哈
The old b-ball.
我也挺喜歡
You know, I've been known to
在周末打打二對二的
get into a little two-on-two on the weekends.
不  我說的是職業球員
No, I meant professional.
我和勇士隊  火箭隊
I've dated a Warrior, a Rocket,
森林狼隊  猛龍隊的隊員都交往過
a Timberwolf, and a Raptor.
所以我是你第一個交往的科技界人士
Oh, so I'm the first tech guy you've ever dated?
是的
Yeah.
跟個不那么大的人約會真有點不同呢
It's gonna be different going out with a guy who's not so huge.
猜猜怎么了
Guess what?
我有一個大驚喜
I have a huge surprise.
-什么  -我要承辦一場晚宴
- What? - I got a catering gig!
你又找到一份工作嗎
You got another job?
你有兩份工作  而我一份都找不到
You have two jobs, I can't even get one!
不不不  我接受那份工作
No, no, no I only took the job
是因為有五千塊的酬勞
because it pays five grand.
五千塊嗎
Five grand?
我得跟那人睡十次才能賺到
I'd have to sleep with that guy 10 times to make that.
好了  冷靜一下  好嗎
Okay, okay, just calm down, all right?
我接受這工作
I only took the gig
是因為這樣就能在你找到工作前養活你
so that I can cover your expenses until you find a job.
棒棒噠
Yay!
加比  你真貼心  但我不能讓你這么做
Gabi, that's very sweet, but I can't let you do that.
很多事情你都不讓我做  可我還是做了
Well, you don't let me do a lot of things, but I still do them.
加比  這不關錢  房租
Gabi, it's not about the money, or rent,
以及有人想要用金錢來交換我的肉體的事
or the fact that someone tried to pay me for sex.
我只是...覺得在這很迷茫  你懂嗎
I just-- I feel lost here, you know?
我什么都沒有
I don't have anything going on.
沒你我要怎么辦
Well, I'll be lost without you,
你不能扔下我  求你別走
you can't leave me. Please don't go.
加比  我沒錢留下來了
Gabi, I can't afford to stay.
好吧  記得我跟你說要采取行動嗎
Okay, remember when I told you to take action?
現在輪到我行動了
Well, it's my turn.
你不許走
You're not leaving!
我接受這份工作  這樣一來就能
I took this job so I can cover your expenses
在之后的幾個月養活你
for the next few months!
我愛你  你不許拒絕我
And I love you, and I will not take no for an answer!
這是人家對我喊的最窩心的一句話了
Well, that's the sweetest thing that's ever been yelled at me.
那你決定留下了嗎
So, you'll stay?
有一個條件
Well, on one condition.
我要在晚宴上給你幫忙
I'm gonna help you with this catering gig.
不用...
No...
-別客氣  我...  -不用麻煩
- No, no, I-- - That's not necessary.
加比  別跟我爭
Gabi, I insist.
我不要做誰的金絲雀
I will not be a kept woman.
我已經體驗過了
Been there, done that.
好嗎  我要幫你一起準備餐點
Okay, I'm gonna help you with this job.
我來當你的副廚  下手  服務員
I'll be your sous chef, your busser, your server,
會在你身邊寸步不離的
I will not leave your side.
另外  這會讓我忘記那個
Plus, you know, it'll help me take my mind off the guy
以為我是妓女的男人
who thought I was a hooker.
會嗎
Will it?
我問你們
Quick question.
要是你用慣了大瓶的橄欖油
If you were used to this big bottle of olive oil,
有人給你個小瓶的橄欖油
someone gave you this smaller bottle of olive oil,
你會對此一笑置之嗎
would you point at it and laugh?
什么
What?
就是說  小瓶的橄欖油
It's just, would you be disappointed
會讓你覺得不滿意嗎
in this smaller bottle of olive oil
盡管這小瓶的橄欖油
even though the smaller bottle of olive oil
聲譽極好  從無差評
never had a complaint?
你怎么突然對橄欖油感興趣了
What's with the sudden interest in olive oil?
尤蘭達  清醒一下吧
Yolanda, wake up
他這是在比喻丁丁的尺寸
and smell the penis metaphor.
我和凱拉約會
It's just, I'm going out with Kayla,
但她只和...大瓶橄欖油約會過
and she's only ever been with... big olive oils.
喬什  那個橄欖油之謎不是真的
Josh, that myth about olive oils isn't true.
她之前的四任男友
The last four guys she dated
都是職業籃球運動員  身高在兩米以上
were professional basketball players all over 6'7".
好吧  你麻煩大了
Oh yeah, you in trouble.
喬什  我的麻煩越來越大了
Josh, my problem just got bigger.
只有你大
Well, that makes one of us!
各位  能給我提點建議嗎
Hey, guys, can I get your advice on something?
見鬼  動感單車搞得我沒法躲開加比
Damn you, soul spin and my inability to get away from Gabi.
你們上了一節動感單車課就疼成這樣嗎
Hey, are you guys still sore from that one soul spin class?
我從沒這么疼過
I've never been in such pain.
都舉不起胳膊了
I can't even lift my arms.
等一下
Wait a minute.
假設你是給我幫忙的服務員
So, if you were a cater waiter assisting me,
你能拿住這托盤嗎
Could you hold this tray?
不能
No.
加比  這主意太好了
Gabi, this was such a great idea!
我都快被一切壓垮了
I've been so stressed out about everything.
是啊  你熱身了嗎
Yeah. Did you stretch?
-沒有  -很好
- No. - Okay, great.
幫我拿下手機  我去拿些毛巾
Hold my phone, I'm gonna get some towels.
加比
Uh, Gabi,
你為什么會接到一個叫
Why are you getting a call
"認為索菲亞是妓女的約翰"的電話
from "John who thought Sofia was a hooker"?
有嗎
Ma-huh?
-加比  快說  -好吧
- Gabi, start talking. - Okay.
我去了酒吧
I went to the hotel bar
因為知道約翰把你當成妓女
because I knew that you were upset
你很傷心
that John called you a hooker.
所以我想當面問他  是不是搞錯了
So, I confronted him, thinking maybe he made a mistake
把給管家的錢給了你
and the money was actually for the housekeeper,
然而并不是
but I was wrong,
他確實認為你是個妓女
he did think you were a hooker.
所以我讓他向你道歉
So, I demanded he apologize,
但他卻問我是不是警察
but then he thought I was a cop,
我只好告訴他我是廚師
so I had to tell him I was a chef,
然后他就給了我個五千塊的餐飲工作
then he offered me a $5,000 catering job,
就是你非要去幫我的那個
which you insisted on helping me with!
所以我就帶你來這兒了
And so now we're here
因為我想如果你來了這兒
because I thought maybe if you came here,
你明天就會疼得上不了班
You'd be too sore to work tomorrow.
真的真的很抱歉
So I'm really really sorry.
天吶  算你走運
Oh my god, oh my god, you are so lucky
我馬上就要騎車泄憤了
that I'm about to pedal off all this rage right now!
請注意  單車學員們
Attention, cyclists,
很抱歉的通知  布拉德生病  課程取消
We're sorry to report Brad is sick and class is canceled.
不是吧
No!
誰都不許走
No one is going anywhere
因為課程可沒取消
because this class is not canceled!
我覺得大家應該聽她的
I think everyone should listen to her.
閉嘴加比  開始蹬車
Stop talking, Gabi, and start pedaling.
誰敢跟我說今天沒課
No one's gonna tell me that there's no class today.
有沒有人跟我一樣受夠了被拒絕
Isn't anyone else just tired of hearing no?
有
Yeah!
有沒有人受夠了求而不得
And aren't you tired of not getting what you want out of life?
有
Yeah!
受夠了被叫做妓女
Sick of being called a hooker?
好吧  忘了最后一條
All right, well, just forget that last one.
現在站起來  我們要爬山了
Now get up, we're on a hill!
快  加油  站起來
Come on, let's go! I said get up!
你是怎么了  你老板對你很刻薄嗎
Oh, what the matter? Is your boss being mean to you?
那試試失業吧
Well, try not having a boss
因為你已經三個月沒工作了
because you've been unemployed for three months!
快點蹬
Pedal faster!
瞧瞧你這一身好裝備
Oh, and look at you in your fancy soul spin gear.
你怎么買得起這些
How could you afford all that?
你跟父母一起住
Do you not have to pay rent
所以不用付房租嗎
because you live with your parents?
我可不會
Well, that's not gonna be me!
-我獨立  我自豪  -沒錯
- Because I enjoy my independence! - Yeah!
-我自由  我驕傲  -沒錯
- I like my freedom! - Yeah!
你們知道這意味著什么嗎
So, you know what that means?
我不搬回佛羅里達了
I'm not moving home to Florida!
不去了嗎
You're not?
對  不去了
No. I guess I'm not.
誰允許你們慢下來了  快蹬
Who said you could slow down? Push ups!
索菲亞  這堂課太棒了
Sofia, that was amazing.
你對我們吼西班牙語時
And when you shouted at us in Spanish,
聽起來更壞了
you sounded even meaner.
天吶  我還說西班牙語了嗎
Oh my god, I was talking in Spanish?
我都沒注意
I didn't even realize.
順口就說了
Something just came over me,
不受自己控制
and I had to take charge, you know?
天吶  再次控場的感覺真好
Oh god, it felt so good to be in control again.
我承辦那晚宴的唯一原因
You know, the only reason I took that catering job
就是想把你留在舊金山  你知道的對嗎
was to keep you here in San Francisco with me, right?
我知道  別擔心
I know. But don't worry.
就像我說的  我哪也不去了
Like I said, I'm not going anywhere.
還不知怎么做到  但是我會解決的
I don't know how, but I will figure it out.
我們一起解決
We'll figure it out.
好的  走吧  我們離開這里
All right, come on, let's get out of here.
我也想
I'd love to, you know,
但我的腿沒知覺了
But I cannot feel my legs!
天吶[西語]
Ay, dios mios!
不用謝
You're welcome.
課上得真棒  你在哪任教
Hey, that was a great class. Where do you teach?
沒有  我只是在基督教青年頻道看過
Oh, I don't. I just take classes at the Y.
你無師自通啊  激勵又訓斥別人
You're a natural. Motivating people and yelling at them?
這真的是天賦
That's a real gift.
-謝謝  -是啊  她在家也這么干
- Thank you. - Yeah, she does it at home, too.
我是這里的首席教練
Well, I'm the head instructor here.
你有興趣來我們這工作嗎
Would you be interested in working for us?
什么
Wha-huh?
她的意思是  是的她有興趣
Uh, what she means is yes! Yes, she would.
-你什么時候能來上班  -現在怎么樣
- How soon can you start? - How's now?
你被錄用了
You're hired.
我在后面的辦公室等你
I'll meet you in the back office
我們談談工資  獎金和福利吧
to talk wage, commission, and benefits.
工資  獎金和福利  天吶
Wage, commission, and benefits, oh my.
好的  我馬上來找你
Okay. I'll see you in a second.
天吶  你又有活干啦
My god, you're a working girl again!
這次是褒義的
And I mean that in the nice way.
看看你擁抱生活以后...
Wow, see what happens when you say yes--
省省吧
Oh, shut up!
能回來真是太好了
It feels good to be back.
沙拉怎么樣
How's your salad?
很棒  我喜歡
Amazing, I love it.
就是橄欖油少了點
It's a little light on the olive oil, though.
給
Here you go.
這是我見過最小瓶的橄欖油
Aww, that is the tiniest bottle of olive oil I've ever seen.
好可愛
It's so cute.
我丁丁尺寸很正常好嗎
I have a perfectly normal-sized penis!
我得走了
I'm gonna go.
那最好
Probably for the best.